[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":68816,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":96736,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</ sub>, yo u start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":7690,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":104428,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1676,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":106105,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3093,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":109198,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":3996,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":113195,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":20240,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":133436,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":2416,"trial_type":"feedba ck","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":135854,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4943,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":140798,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1192,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":141991,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than  6, that 's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3020,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":145011,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":976,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":145988,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2161,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":148149,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":863,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":149012,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":1762,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":150775,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":819,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":151594,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6< /sub> 3?  <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":1860,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":153454,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":718,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":154173,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2412,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":156586,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":642,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":157229,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":1833,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":159063,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":619,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":159683,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2899,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":162583,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0 because 3 + 3 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1062,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":163645,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum i s smalle r than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":1973,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":165618,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 3 because 1 + 2 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":764,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":166383,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2354,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":168738,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 4 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 6 = 4.","rt":718,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":169456,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2254,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":171710,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0 because 4 + 2 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":656,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":172367,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0  +<sub>6 </sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":1525,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":173892,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 2 because 0 + 2 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":771,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":174663,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2948,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":177611,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2 because 3 + 5 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":773,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":178384,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2238,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":180622,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 because 1 + 4 = 5  and 5 is  less than 6.","rt":2457,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":183080,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":1860,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":184941,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0 because 5 + 1 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":820,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":185762,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add  the seco nd one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":1626,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":187388,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 1 because 1 + 0 = 1 and 1 is less than 6.","rt":750,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":188139,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":1471,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":189611,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 1 because 5 + 2 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":751,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":190363,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":14754,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":205118,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a  number i s the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":12407,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":217526,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":5957,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":223483,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1354,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":224837,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":1857,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":226694,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":820,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":227514,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2945,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":230459,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1098,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":231557,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":1929,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":233486,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity un der +<su b>6</sub>.","rt":741,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":234227,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":2051,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":236278,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1585,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":237863,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, the inverse of 0 is 0, the inverse of 1 is 5 and the inverse of 5 is 1, the inverse of 2 is 4 and the inverse  of 4 is  2, and finally the inverse of 3 is 3. Do you see a relationship between an element and its inverse under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"They all add up to 6?","response_history":["They all add up the ","They all add up the","They all add up th","They all add up to 6?"],"rt":73155,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":311018,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":8211,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":319232,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can  make eve ry other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":28246,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":347479,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":60862,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":408342,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":4309,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":412653,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":4111,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":416765,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6< /sub> 5,  1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":6985,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":423751,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":3420,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":427172,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1855,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":429027,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":3272,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":432299,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1137,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":433436,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, 1 and 5 are generators. However, 0, 2, 3, and 4 are not generators. Try playing with these non-generators and seeing which elements each of them does generate (i.e. which elements you can get by combining each n on-gener ator with itself repeatedly). Do you see relationships among particular subsets of the elements that are not generators under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Only the outliers are generators under +6","response_history":["Only the outliers are generators and ","Only the outliers are generators and","Only the outliers are generators an","Only the outliers are generators a","Only the outliers are generators under +6"],"rt":111225,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":544661,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After t hat, try  to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":18603,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":563267,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3933,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":567202,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1047,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":568249,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":4507,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":572756,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 7 + <sub>9</ sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3320,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":576076,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2428,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":578505,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3403,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":581909,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3627,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":585536,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"4+1 = 5 which is less than 9 so we leave it alone and don't subtract anything.","response_history":["5 because it is le","5 because ","4+1 is","4+1 i","4+1 ","4+1 = 5 which is less than 9 so we leave it alone and don't subtract anything."],"rt":47668,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":633205,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"8+4 = 12 which is more than 9 so we subtract from that and are left with 3.","response_history":["8+4 is ","8+4 is","8+4 i=","8+4 i","8+4 = 12,","8+4 = 12 which is more than 9 so we subtract from that an d are le ft with 4","8+4 = 12 which is more than 9 so we subtract from that and are left with 3 which is ","8+4 = 12 which is more than 9 so we subtract from that and are left with 3 whic","8+4 = 12 which is more than 9 so we subtract from that and are left with 3 whi","8+4 = 12 which is more than 9 so we subtract from that and are left with 3 wh","8+4 = 12 which is more than 9 so we subtract from that and are left with 3 w","8+4 = 12 which is more than 9 so we subtract from that and are left with 3 ","8+4 = 12 which is more than 9 so we subtract from that and are left with 3."],"rt":37102,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":670310,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"If the sum is smaller than 9 then that is the result, if more than 9 we subtract 9 to get the resu lt.","response_history":["If the sum is smaller than 9 then that is the result, if more than 9 we subtract 9 t","If the sum is smaller than 9 then that is the result, if more than 9 we subtract 9 o ","If the sum is smaller than 9 then that is the result, if more than 9 we subtract 9 o","If the sum is smaller than 9 then that is the result, if more than 9 we subtract 9 to getr ","If the sum is smaller than 9 then that is the result, if more than 9 we subtract 9 to getr","If the sum is smaller than 9 then that is the result, if more than 9 we subtract 9 to get the result."],"rt":127607,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":797918,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":16367,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":814288,"internal_chunk_id":"0- 0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":5496,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":819785,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6 because 3 + 6 = 9.","response_history":["5 ","5","7","6 because 3 +","6 because 3 ","6 because 3 + 6 = 9 which ","6 because 3 + 6 = 9 which","6 because 3 + 6 = 9 whic","6 because 3 + 6 = 9 whi","6 because 3 + 6 = 9 wh","6 because 3 + 6 = 9 w","6 because 3 + 6 = 9 ","6 because 3 + 6 = 9."],"rt":34293,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":854078,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you  got your  answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No because there is not a way to make certain numbers with 2 as a generator under +9.","response_history":["No because there is not a way to make certain numbers with 2 as a generator under _","No because there is not a way to make certain numbers with 2 as a generator under +90","No because there is not a way to make certain numbers with 2 as a generator under +9."],"rt":61583,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":915663,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes because we can make every other number using it.","response_history":["Yes because we can make every other number using it."],"rt":157644,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1073310,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No because there is no way to make every other number.","response_history":["No because there is no way to make certain ","No because there is no way to make ce","No because there is no way to make c","No because there is no way to make every other number."],"rt":25291,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1098603,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No because there is no way to make every number.","response_history":["No because there is no way to make every nu,mb","No because there is no way to make every nu,m","No because there is no way to make every  nu,","N o because there is no way to make every number."],"rt":14581,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1113185,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":21003,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1134189,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1 +n 4 = n","response_history":["1 +n =","1 +n 4 = n, I don","1 +n 4 = n"],"rt":92498,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1226690,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"x +n x = x, because x and n can be any counting number.","response_history":["x +n x = x, I'm not ","x +n x = x, I'm","x +n x = x, I'","x +n x = x, I","x +n x = x, because x and n can be any counting number."],"rt":41628,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":1268320,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I don't know.","response_history":["I don't know."],"rt":15132,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":1283453,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":3849,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":1287305,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":3459,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":89,"time_elapsed":1290764,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":3772,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":90,"time_elapsed":1294536,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"True because it still needs to equal +n, I'm not really sure at all though.","response_history":["True because it still needs to equal n","True because it still needs to equal +m, ","True because it still needs to equal +m,","True because it still needs to equal +m","True because it still needs to equal +n, I'm not really sure at all thoguh","True because it still needs to equal +n, I'm not really sure at all thogu","True because it still needs to equal +n, I'm not really sure at all thog","True because it still needs to equal +n, I'm not really sure at all though."],"rt":38554,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":91,"time_elapsed":1333091,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":3801,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":92,"time_elapsed":1336892,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"Sometimes, it depends on the formula? I'm not sure at all.","response_history":["Sometimes, it depends on the formula? I'm not sure at all."],"rt":44782,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":93,"time_elapsed":1381674,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":4416,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":94,"time_elapsed":1386093,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":1432,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":95,"time_elapsed":1387526,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"29","response_history":["29"],"rt":2052,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":96,"time_elapsed":1389579,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"High school diploma","response_history":["High school diploma"],"rt":6543,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":97,"time_elapsed":1396122,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Not sure, maybe pre-algebra. I didn't complete high-school and later got a GED, I have very little advanced math experience and wasn't really ever taught.","response_history":["Pre-ale","Pre-algebra, I s","Pre -algebra , I ","Pre-algebra, I didn't complete H","Pre-algebra, I didn't complete high-school and en","Pre-algebra, I didn't complete high-school and e","Pre-algebra, I didn't complete high-school and later got a GER","Pre-algebra, I didn't complete high-school and later got a GED, I have very little math experience at least in advanc","Pre-algebra, I didn't complete high-school and later got a GED, I have very little ma","Pre-algebra, I didn't complete high-school and later got a GED, I have very little m","Pre-algebra, I didn't complete high-school and later got a GED, I have very little advanced math experience.","N, I didn't complete high-school and later got a GED, I have very little advanced math experience.","Not, I didn't complete high-school and later got a GED, I have very little advanced math experience.","Not , I didn't complete high-school and later got a GED, I have very little advanced math experience.","Not su, I didn't complete high-school and later got a GED, I have  very li ttle advanced math experience.","Not sur, I didn't complete high-school and later got a GED, I have very little advanced math experience.","Not sure, I didn't complete high-school and later got a GED, I have very little advanced math experience.","Not sure,, I didn't complete high-school and later got a GED, I have very little advanced math experience.","Not sure, , I didn't complete high-school and later got a GED, I have very little advanced math experience.","Not sure, ma, I didn't complete high-school and later got a GED, I have very little advanced math experience.","Not sure, may, I didn't complete high-school and later got a GED, I have very little advanced math experience.","Not sure, mayb, I didn't complete high-school and later got a GED, I have very little advanced math experience.","Not sure, maybe, I didn't complete high-school and later got a GED, I have very little advanced math experience.","Not sure, maybe , I didn't complete high-school and later got a GED,  I have  very little advanced math experience.","Not sure, maybe pr, I didn't complete high-school and later got a GED, I have very little advanced math experience.","Not sure, maybe pre, I didn't complete high-school and later got a GED, I have very little advanced math experience.","Not sure, maybe pre , I didn't complete high-school and later got a GED, I have very little advanced math experience.","Not sure, maybe pre a, I didn't complete high-school and later got a GED, I have very little advanced math experience.","Not sure, maybe pre al, I didn't complete high-school and later got a GED, I have very little advanced math experience.","Not sure, maybe pre alg, I didn't complete high-school and later got a GED, I have very little advanced math experience.","Not sure, maybe pre alge, I didn't complete high-school and later got a GED, I have very little advanced math experience.","Not sure, maybe pre algeb, I didn't complete high-school and later got a GED, I have very little advan ced math  experience.","Not sure, maybe pre algebr, I didn't complete high-school and later got a GED, I have very little advanced math experience.","Not sure, maybe pre algebra, I didn't complete high-school and later got a GED, I have very little advanced math experience.","Not sure, maybe pre algebra. I didn't complete high-school and later got a GED, I have very little advanced math experience.","Not sure, maybe prealgebra. I didn't complete high-school and later got a GED, I have very little advanced math experience.","Not sure, maybe pre-algebra. I didn't complete high-school and later got a GED, I have very little advanced math experience.","Not sure, maybe pre-algebra. I didn't complete high-school and later got a GED, I have very little advanced math experience and wasn't relly","Not sure, maybe pre-algebra. I didn't complete high-school and later got a GED, I have very little advanced math experience and wasn't rell","Not sure, maybe pre-algebra. I didn't complete high-scho ol and l ater got a GED, I have very little advanced math experience and wasn't rel","Not sure, maybe pre-algebra. I didn't complete high-school and later got a GED, I have very little advanced math experience and wasn't really ever taught."],"rt":105429,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":98,"time_elapsed":1501552,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":4843,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":99,"time_elapsed":1506397,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"mu lti","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":3183,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":100,"time_elapsed":1509581,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":6847,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":101,"time_elapsed":1516429,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":4859,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":102,"time_elapsed":1521289,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2289,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":103,"time_elapsed":1523578,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","response_history":["Male"],"rt":1971,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":104,"time_elapsed":1525550,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":5229,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":105,"time_elapsed":1530780,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No I did not.","response_history":["No I did not."],"rt":6696,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":106,"time_elapsed":1537476,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I'm sure you'll get a laugh at some of my answers, I honestly did try though!","response_history":["I'm sure you'll get a laugh at some of my answers, I d","I'm sure you'll get a laugh at some of my answers, I honestly did try though!"],"rt":33479,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":107,"time_elapsed":1570955,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"}]